couponminister.in 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy - CouponMinister

By using the website, CouponMinister ([www.couponminister.in](http://www.couponminister.in/)), you consent to our website’s privacy policy and CouponMinister website [terms of use](http://www.couponminister.in/terms-of-use/ "CouponMinister's Terms of Use ").

**Information we collect from you** : We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or register on our website. While doing so, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We use your information in one of the following ways:**

  * To personalize user experience
  * To improve our website
  * To process and record coupon requesting and redemption activity.
  * To understand usage trends and preferences.
  * To send periodic emails
  * To send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

_Note_ : We include detailed unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email, in case at any time you wish to unsubscribe from receiving future emails.

**We protect your information:** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. However, as no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

**We use cookies:** We send one or more cookies (a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your computer. A cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Sites. These cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different. Please review your browser’s Help menu to learn how to modify your cookies setup.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**No sale or transfer of information to outside parties:** We do not sell, disclose or transfer any information to outside parties, except in the following conditions:

  * Information could be transmitted to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website or conducting our business so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
  * Information could also be disclosed when release is appropriate or required to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
  * Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party websites’ links** : We include and offer third party products or services on our website. The third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nevertheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about the third party websites.

**Children’s online privacy** : We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:   **If and when there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will post the same on this page.
